<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.3/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.3/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.3.xsd" version="0.3" xml:lang="en">

    <page>
        <title>Aalst</title>
        <id>18008</id>
        <revision>
            <id>747320</id>
            <timestamp>2008-01-19T00:50:20Z</timestamp>
            <contributor>
                <username>Wandering</username>
                <id>13268</id>
                <realname>Wandering</realname>
            </contributor>
            <minor/>
            <comment>isIn</comment>
            <text xml:space="preserve">'''Aalst''' is in [[East Flanders]], in [[Belgium]]. A medium sized town, by Belgian standards, with a population of around 77,000 people, Aalst is located right between the larger city of [[Ghent]] (''Gent'') and the capital, [[Brussels]].

                Travel by train from Brussels, it takes about 25 minutes.

                ==Get around==

                ==See==

                ==Do==

                ==Buy==

                ==Eat==

                ==Drink==

                ==Sleep==

                ==Get out==

                {{outline}}
                {{isIn|East_Flanders}}
            </text>
        </revision>
    </page>


    <page>
        <title>Abergavenny</title>
        <id>69560</id>
        <revision>
            <id>1367943</id>
            <timestamp>2010-01-31T04:53:27Z</timestamp>
            <contributor>
                <username>Dguillaime</username>
                <id>26409</id>
                <realname>D. Guillaime</realname>
            </contributor>
            <minor/>
            <comment>Reverted edits by [[Special:Contributions/82.13.12.150|82.13.12.150]] ([[User talk:82.13.12.150|Talk]]) to last version by [[User:Owain|Owain]]</comment>
            <text xml:space="preserve">'''Abergavenny''' is a town in [[Monmouthshire]].

                [[Image:Abergavenny.jpg|thumb|Abergavenny, Monmouthshire]]
                ==Understand==
                A thriving town, '''Abergavenny''' is the gateway to South Wales where you can enjoy a relaxing short break or longer holiday amidst stunning countryside.  The town itself is set against the '''Brecon Beacons National Park''' and '''Black Mountains''', ideal for breathtaking walks and scenery and is nestled within the beautiful Usk Valley.

                ==See==
                *'''Abergavenny Castle''' dates back to 1087 and makes for a fascinating visit.

                ==Do==
                *'''Abergavenny Museum''' is set in the grounds of Norman Castle.  If it’s a nice day, take a picnic, otherwise simply learn about the history of this historic market town.

                ==Buy==
                One of the most well-known markets in Wales, '''Abergavenny’s Tuesday market''' has more than 200 stalls offering a huge array of goods.  In addition there is a Friday and Saturday market and the occasional craft fair, flea market and antique fair.

                ==Eat==
            </text>
        </revision>
    </page>

    <page>
        <title>Adirondacks</title>
        <id>3516</id>
        <revision>
            <id>1334033</id>
            <timestamp>2009-12-28T17:11:21Z</timestamp>
            <contributor>
                <username>Geoflaneur</username>
                <id>3418</id>
                <realname>geoFlaneur</realname>
            </contributor>
            <comment>/* Other destinations */</comment>
            <text xml:space="preserve">[[Image:Giant's Washbasin.jpg|thumb|320px|A small mountain lake east of the High Peaks]]

                The '''Adirondack Park''' is both the largest and the first government-protected park in the contiguous [[United States of America|United States]]. It covers a vast expanse&amp;mdash;bigger than [[New Hampshire]]&amp;mdash;of rugged, thickly wooded, mountainous terrain in northeast [[New York (state)|New York State]]. The Adirondacks are a popular destination for all lovers of outdoor activities, from hiking and skiing to ice and rock climbing.

                ==Regions==
                * [[Keene Valley]] -- Great rock and ice climbing.
                * [[Champlain Valley]] -- The &quot;sixth&quot; Great Lake, this spectacular Lake Champlain marks the frontier between New York State and Vermont.

                ==Cities==

                * [[Chester (New York)|Town of Chester]] - Chestertown plus several surrounding hamlets and lakeside communities on the other side of the Northway from Lake George
                * [[Jay (New York)|Jay]]
                * [[Lake Placid]] - Former host to the Winter Olympics, it's now a charming, but pricey tourist town.
                * [[Malone (New York)|Malone]]
                * [[Old Forge]] - A very small town that is the gateway to the Adirondacks from the Mohawk Valley and a starting point for the Northern Forest Canoe Trail
                * [[Saranac Lake]] - All American City
                * [[Ticonderoga]] - Home of Fort Ticonderoga, a Revolutionary War Site.
                * [[Tupper Lake]] - Home of the Natural History Museum Of The Adirondacks.
                * [[Wilmington (New York)|Wilmington]]

                ==Other destinations==
                [[Image:Montcalm Point on Lake George.jpg|thumb|280px|Montcalm Point on Lake George]]

                * [[Lake George]] -- Vacation spot in upstate New York situated on a lake.
                * Historic [[Essex (New York)]] -- Charming Federal town situated at the border of the Adirondack Park and Lake Champlain. Visitors enjoy well preserved architecture from the early 1800s, galleries, marinas, ferry to [[Vermont]], seasonal dining and accommodations and convenient access to the [[Champlain Area Trails]] network.
                * Adirondack Scenic Railroad

                ==Understand==
                ===History===

                ===Landscape===

                ===Flora and fauna===

                ===Climate===

                ==Talk==

                ==Get in==
                [[Image:Southeastern High Peaks from Giant Mountain.jpg|thumb|280px|The High Peaks from Giant Mountain]]
                ===By car===
                The main route along the eastern edge of the Adirondacks is Interstate 87, commonly known as &quot;the Northway.&quot;  The Northway has beautiful views of the mountains, but limited services north of Lake George.

                The main roads around the High Peaks region are Route 73 to the north and east which runs through Lake Placid, routes 3 and 30 through Tupper Lake to the west, and route 28N and Boreas road to the South.  Gas stations are available about every 20 miles in these areas.

                ===By bus===
                There is limited service by bus from Rochester, Syracuse and Albany to points north including Keene Valley, Lake Placid, Tupper Lake and Plattsburgh. This service is provided by &quot;Trailways&quot; bus service.

                ===By train===
                '''Amtrak's'''[http://www.amtrak.com] aptly named &quot;Adirondack&quot; train runs between [[Montreal]], [[Quebec]] and Penn Station in [[New York City]] with a stop in [[Ticonderoga]] plus other stops that connect with local shuttles to nearby destinations. The train leaves Montreal at 9:30AM daily, and New York at 8:30AM. The trip takes approximately 10 hours but expect delays at the border.

                ==Fees/Permits==

                Except for improved public campgrounds, there is no fee to camp or travel on state land.

                ==Get around==

                ==See==

                ==Do==
                *&lt;do name=&quot;Adirondack Equine Center&quot; alt=&quot;Ausable Equine Center&quot; address=&quot;Route 373 Ausable Chasm, NY&quot; directions=&quot;Ausable Chasm Trailrides - Lake Placid Sleigh Rides&quot; phone=&quot;518-834-9933&quot; url=&quot;www.adirondackequinecenter.com&quot; hours=&quot;All year round&quot; price=&quot;&quot; lat=&quot;&quot; long=&quot;&quot;&gt;Lake Placid Sleigh Rides, Ausable Chasm Horseback Trail Rides, Horse Drawn Carriage Rides.  We have some of the most gentle horses you will ever find and they are always treated with love, trust, and respect.  Personalized attention given and a free lesson prior to ride. Children Welcome. www.adirondackequinecenter.com&lt;/do&gt;

                *'''Lake Placid Center for the Arts''' is a gallery and theater

                *'''Lake George Steamboat Cruises''' offers historic and scenic one-hour cruises.


                ==Buy==

                ==Eat==

                ==Drink==

                ==Sleep==
                Get a tent, sleep almost anywhere.

                ==Stay safe==
                There is very little crime in the Adirondacks.  The most common problem is travelers going into the wilderness without proper experience or equipment. There is prevalent wildlife throughout the Adirondacks, and interactions between humans and wild animals is common.

                  In some areas bear resistant canisters are required.  Check the areas where you are staying to see if this is the case.

                ==Get out==




                {{outline}}
                {{isIn|New_York_%28state%29}}
                {{regionguide}}
                {{parkguide}}
                [[extra:adirondacks]]
                [[de:Adirondack Mountains]]
                [[Wikipedia:Adirondack Park]]
            </text>
        </revision>
    </page>

    <page>
        <title>Adjara</title>
        <id>49226</id>
        <revision>
            <id>578261</id>
            <timestamp>2007-06-04T21:15:10Z</timestamp>
            <contributor>
                <username>Peterfitzgerald</username>
                <id>12794</id>
                <realname>Peter Fitzgerald</realname>
            </contributor>
            <minor/>
            <comment>#REDIRECT [[Southwestern Georgia]]</comment>
            <text xml:space="preserve">#REDIRECT [[Southwestern Georgia]]</text>
        </revision>
    </page>
    <page>
        <title>Adjaria</title>
        <id>49229</id>
        <revision>
            <id>578314</id>
            <timestamp>2007-06-04T22:00:06Z</timestamp>
            <contributor>
                <ip>69.251.227.214</ip>
            </contributor>
            <comment>#REDIRECT [[Southwestern Georgia]]</comment>
            <text xml:space="preserve">#REDIRECT [[Southwestern Georgia]]</text>
        </revision>
    </page>


    <page>
    <title>Atwater (Ohio)</title>
    <id>42573</id>
    <revision>
        <id>1298136</id>
        <timestamp>2009-11-17T10:00:05Z</timestamp>
        <contributor>
            <username>Huttite</username>
            <id>361</id>
            <realname />
        </contributor>
        <minor/>
        <comment>[[Atwater Township]] moved to [[Atwater (Ohio)]] over redirect: Atwater (Ohio) is the simplest English name, as used in the article. Township is superfluous and not a disambiguator.</comment>
        <text xml:space="preserve">'''Atwater''' is a township in southeast [[Portage County]].

            ==Get in==
            SR 244, which runs east and west across most of Ohio, and SR 183, which runs from [[Ravenna (Ohio)|Ravenna]] to [[Carroll County]] intersect in Atwater.

            From Interstate 76, take the Edinburg exit, go northwest on SR 14, to SR 183 South.

            From SR 44 take SR 224 east in [[Randolph Township|Randolph]].

            ==Get around==

            ==See==

            ==Do==

            ==Buy==

            ==Eat==
              * '''Sports Pizza''', 1281 State Route 183 (SR 183 and Waterloo Road), tel: ''+1'' 330-947-2288.   This restaurant, in an old colonial-style house, is the biggest in Atwater.  They have karaoke on various nights, and a bar inside.

            * '''Subway''', 1304 State Route 183 (inside Circle K), tel: ''+1'' 330-947-3400.  There is one picnic table outside.

            ==Drink==

            ==Sleep==
            There is one campground in Atwater, but no hotels or inns.  Nearby [[Alliance (Ohio)|Alliance]] or [[Kent (Ohio)|Kent]] would be your best bet for lodging.

            * '''Whispering Pines Campground''', 1085 Industry Rd, tel: ''+1'' 330-947-3504.

            ==Get out==

            {{outline}}
            {{IsIn|Portage_County}}

            [[Wikipedia:Atwater_Township,_Portage_County,_Ohio]]
        </text>
    </revision>
    </page>


    <page>
    <title>Massanjore</title>
    <id>73658</id>
    <revision>
    <id>1272241</id>
    <timestamp>2009-10-16T16:14:30Z</timestamp>
    <contributor>
        <ip>117.194.226.58</ip>
    </contributor>
    <comment>/* Do */</comment>
    <text xml:space="preserve">[[Image:Masanjore Dam 1.jpg|right|thumb|250px|Massanjore Dam]]

    '''Massanjore''' is a city in [[Jharkhand]].

    Massanjore dam, across the Mayurakshi River, is in Dumka district of Jharkhand State. Built with Candian aid, it is also called Canada Dam or Pearson Dam. It was commissioned in 1956.

    The dam is 155 feet high from its base and is 2170 feet long. The reservoir has an area of 16,650 acres when full and has a storage capacity of 500,000 acre feet. Apart from the Massanjore Dam there is a barrage at Tilpara, near Siuri. The barrage is 1,013 feet long.

    ==Get in==
    It is about 31 km from Dumka in Jharkhand and is about 45 km from Siuri in West Bengal. It is on the Siuri-Dumka road. Buses ply on this road.

    ==Get around==
    Walk or have your own transport.

    It is very useful.

    ==Do==
    the place is just amazing.the broad river,mountains,proper jharkhand gives its identity everywhere.at night,the total ambiance changes.rock climbing or swimming is pretty much enjoying.

    ==Buy==

    ==Eat==
    There are few food stalls which are situated near the dam.to get food at night,u have to arrange within afternoon.rate is pretty cheap.

==Drink==
cold drinks are available near the shops beside the dam.if u can manage the regional &quot;mahua&quot; from the tribal villages,it will be an awesome combination.

==Sleep==
* '''Youth Hostel''', two km from the dam. Double rooms cost Rs 100 per night. There is a 22-bed dormitory. Beds cost Rs 40 per night. For bookings contact: Yuva Kalyan Office, 32/1, BBD Bag (South), Kolkata 700001, Phone +91 33 22480626
* '''Mayurakshi Bhavan''' of the Irrigation Department, Govt. of West Bengal. A double-bed room costs Rs 300 per night. For bookings contact: Deputy Secretary, Irrigation Department, Water Resource, Development Building, Salt Lake City, Kolkata, Phone +91 33 23212259.
* '''Jharkhand Tourist Lodge'''.

==Contact==

==Get out==
* '''[[Deoghar]]''' - 98 km
* '''[[Santiniketan]]''' - 75 km

{{IsPartOf|Santhal Parganas}}
{{outline}}
{{cityguide}}</text>
    </revision>
    </page>




</mediawiki>